Earl "Marcus" Lampley

Bethlehem, Georgia 30620 | 404-626-4528 | Marcusdlampley@live.com

Summary

Earl "Marcus" Lampley: I am a life long learner. I have a passion for technology in both hardware and recently software design. I have experience in communication, education, technical solutions, and have recently taken a software coding boot camp to learn several coding languages and skills as a full stack developer. I will use my drive for learning and my skills to be the solution you need.

Skills

- Collaboration
- Full Stack Development
- React
- React-Native
- Python
- Teaching

- Technical Support
- JavaScript
- PostgreSQL
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Express

Experience

Substitute Teacher | 08/2019 to Current

Barrow County Public Schools - Georgia

- Maintained student attendance and assignment records to prevent lapses during teacher absences.
- Known for being flexible when the school had multiple assignments in the same school day

Engineering Fellow | 09/2020 to 10/2020

GA SEI, Software Engineering Immersive

- Create full websites and programs using several strategies and technologies, JS, Express, React, Python, Django, GitHub, Heroku, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB.
- Working as a team to work through issues and participate in group problem solving
- Continued work on applications through React Native, and Unity as passion projects.

Teacher | 09/2015 to 05/2019

Gwinnett County Public Schools + Savannah Chatham - Georgia

- Taught between 20 36 students over many subjects. (Economics, Psychology, Sociology, 10th and 12th Grade Literature)
- Upheld all rules and regulations in order to maintain a positive learning environment and to minimize distractions.
- Known for being flexible when the school needed multiple subjects to be handled by a single teacher.
- Working as a team to work through issues and participate in group planning, and assessment.
- Created lesson plans in accordance with state curriculum and school-wide curriculum standards.
- Taught an after-school enrichment program.

Education and Training

General Assembly - | Certificate of Completion | Software Engineering
Georgia College and State University - - Milledgeville, Ga | | Bachelor of Arts History
University of North Georgia - - Dahlonega, GA | | Master of Arts Teaching

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/earl-lampley-02119638/
- http://lampley-marcus.surge.sh/